A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 2000-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series XIV: Virginia Taskforce for Business Development in the Near East, 2005., Extent: 1 folder. (Folder 6)
  This series contains the records of "A Day in Richmond" and "Norfolk Port Day," two events in 2005 designed to showcase Virginia's agricultural products and the Port of Norfolk to trade attaches from Near Eastern and North African communities. Both events were designed to stimulate trade between Virginia and Near Eastern nations such as Libya, Greece, Algeria, and the Arab Republic of Egypt, among others. The intended goals of the "A Day in Richmond" event were to establish contacts with foreign emissaries, improve trade with Middle Eastern, North African, and Mediterranean countries, and to gain an appreciation for the views of the region's diplomats. The overall goal of "Norfolk Port Day" was to demonstrate Virginia's capacity for handling trade with foreign countries. Records of these events include schedules, guest lists, logistical information, and drafts of follow-up letters thanking participants and guests.
  - A Day in Richmond, 2005. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Norfolk Port Day, 2005. (Box 6, Folder 6)